# **Aroon Salotra**

## Software Engineer

↓ 07397377081 ★ aroonsalotra@gmail.com ★ https://www.aroonsalotra.com/in www.linkedin.com/in/aroon-salotra ♠ https://github.com/AroonSalotra

#### **Profile**

Self-taught programmer ready to test my abilities - I am able to create applications that integrate with REST APIs with a focus on best industry practises to deliver a clean and efficient user experience. At my current job, I maintain the company website & manage financial data for clientele.

## Skills

HTML | CSS

React

Javascript

Typescript

Redux

Git

Figma

Node.js

## **Work Experience**

**Junior Web Developer** 2023 – present

Countrywide Tax & Trust

Trading Assistant Feb 2021 – 2023

Sainsbury's

#### **Education**

Game Design, University of Northampton

Sep 2018 – Jul 2020

2:1 Qualification

### **Projects**

**To-Do,** https://to-do-vert-psi.vercel.app/ □

Project Management application with auth

Deal-IO Game Finder, https://aroonsalotra.github.io/game-deals/ ☑

Game & sale finder using Cheapshark API

Workout App, https://aroonsalotra.github.io/workout-app/ ☑

Program to help beginners choose and understand popular fitness routines.

Covid App, https://aroonsalotra.github.io/covid-app/ ☑

App to showcase Covid deaths and case statistics. Includes an option to sort by Alphabetical, Highest and Lowest cases.

Clicker Game, https://aroonsalotra.github.io/clicker-game/ ☑

Click to defeat enemies which scale based on character level, each kill awards XP and gold - can be spent in shop.